[Music]
I came across this game right here I
feel like games like Arc or you know the
forest or anything that's like open
world and you know involves building and
hunting and survival and all that stuff
then definitely check this game out it's
a demo on
Steam probably just get to the spot then
before it gets like
nighttime is that a wolf
oh I hell
missed oh damn son
oh
what
sh
what L is full
flashlight it's actually pretty good
I'm going to go run into
this yeah I searching I
searching going to freeze it's even got
like cool Frost stunning
right all right we got to find a
um a place to put a a
tent so do you think one person can
sleep
I think so could try for
science renovate on to sleep yeah one on
to sleep there we go no I just jumped
into to as
well o there we go you are well rested
but I'm freezing my butt
off I think you're going to
appreciate cougar in here no okay
I like that it actually Sparks as well
when you're going for the
Flint did how much we need oh we already
got enough yeah I think we
did turn the light off no dead bodies in
here
nope well not important ones for us to
loot
eight more Stone you know these
characters must be so
cold
leing thanks for subing backing
me um
it's getting
cold do you need more
wood uh I have five left I just need to
do the uh roof
yeah uh or campfire I don't think we can
build campfires yet can we we should
yeah you can craft one
I'm going to unload some stuff okay
ooh I think I put the door on
backwards that's
actually
no this is actually the right way for
security reasons
but it opens towards the steps and you
hit your head on it it's
okay at least if there's a fire inside
we can kick the door out and people
can't just kick in that's true
yeah why hello thank you so much for
joining me as game Ed we're jumping in
and testing out permafrost where we
embark on a brutal journey of survival
in a Perpetual winter now the story is
that something hit the moon and it's
cause this effect where the entire world
has gone to a permafrost and it's darn
cold all
right a freaking rabbit or something
there what is that on the side it's a
freaking
rabbit a fast little [__]
too uhhuh maybe I should get the other
elk
too oh dude leveled up on that sucker
okay so can I get my arrow back I can
nice so we need to use our knife that
was three we can skin
it and then search pretty simple and
take all we got ourselves some animal
fats useful for crafting cooking adding
richness to meals and helping crafting
and Port survival TOS of course hide we
know what that is bones and meat we also
knew what fat was but you know it is
what it is I might oh look at that
freaking moon like they're talking about
let's turn off for light that is
absolutely gorgeous but boy wow what
devastation I'm not sure where the hell
hit that maybe a big meteor maybe just
exploded I don't
know right hand side flashlight build
mode h b b for building
gamees all right maybe we can use this
area
here as good as any right I mean why
not oh so you click and it just starts
building good thing is I already had
some wood on me now he just suppose we
only need
two put that
up going to need more wood for
sure a little bit delay for building
everything but if you're building enough
times you kind of nice to see things
being put together hi and welcome to
permafrost so guys this game has you in
permanent
winter and yeah he doesn't have anything
so let's try to get out of
here up and I'm not going to go into the
cave cuz right now I don't know what's
out there so we're going to go to the
Hunter's Glade so we're going to follow
the exclamation
point and that is leading us down that
way so as you can see right now it's
-3 and there is a map so as we we
progress along it will get bigger and
bigger but right now I don't know how
much we're going to be able to do
considering well yes this is just a
demo but I did notice that there is a
demo outline I'm going to show you on
the map after what I'm talking about the
only thing is I want to make sure that
we don't get too cold now there is some
Frost that you're going to see like it
looks really really foggy I advise you
stay out of that unless you have no
other choice
cuz it gets to like- 70 something in
that and yeah the stuff that you're
wearing will not keep you
warm oh
wow okay I think something happened in
here
oh
man
oh let's search he got some money on
him
wow oh a
recording that rabbit's like underneath
the snow right now that is a big Hungry
Bear we're going to take a left away
from that he might be in a fence and
stuff but
um I made a mistake and I dropped the
ammo inside my storage chest by mistake
I guess when I swapped out my clothes
I'm not sure what happened he looks like
he might be super hungry is this do I
have to go in this one oh [__] I might
have to take him
out we're going trying to avoid it oh
another frozen body some more cash and
stuff again go and purchase some stuff
up I
think uh
oh okay this is the bunker
right it must be am I on it right
now seems like
it oh god oh he's
angry oh [__] oh Jesus Murphy this is
going to go
bad I don't think I'm destroying or even
touching this bear with any of those
shots it doesn't seem to be a reaction
to him or
anything it's so tough to see
too oh I want hit him oh he's
pissed she kept fitting here no way he
can fit in
here no way he can fit in here holy [__]
I think I putop myself a little bit
there oh [__] bu he almost got me
through the
stairs oh oh for a second I thought you
know what I can climb
stairs I'm coming for you all right he's
been uh non-stop I'm not sure how many I
got well landed quite a few of them
actually got a couple more head shots on
them
cuz he got over there just a little bit
stuck
is H he's dead oh come on okay I was
like I can't see
him
so yeah see this is like a bad little
place
here that's
where oh freaking a
freaking hey that better be like 200
pieces of meat and I'm going to have to
call dog to come in and eat the rest of
it oh my God like so many
arrows wow look at this this is
beautiful though nicely done find Robin
on the red Tower I'm guessing that's
what this
is oh
[__] like an animal running around there
give the dog raw
meat I don't have any of
that holy [__] look at this
town okay what is going on here the rift
cave I am intrigued by this
game I'm not quite sure what exactly I'm
playing yet but boy oh
boy got a watchtower that I can't get up
into okay I thought I could get up there
there's a weird ass rock down here with
some stones in
it who's
that okay there's something up there got
buildings up there we've got Towers over
there we've
got that like a telecommunications thing
over there I'm not sure man there's a
lot to take in right now
got
him got him got
two okay
perfect me see if I have to do I have to
axe these guys up or what's going on Old
the skinn deer search okay let's take
all whatever I can take let's take
it all right we've got some stuff here
some
Meats hello Pooch hey pooch
got a little pack and everything
here are we friends
now hold the
pet oh [__] yeah I got
Rex okay open inventory
here and now I can put some stuff inside
of him I don't not like that you freaks
let's put the gear in here
holy [__] that's loud hey we can summon
the dog now okay there he comes look at
him there he is holy [__] he's booking
it